{
    "subject": "resource/Rize_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/director",
    "object": "resource/David_LaChapelle",
    "human_readable": "The director of the film 'Rize' is David LaChapelle.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9651920795440674,
            "question": "Which film was directed by David LaChapelle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9430553913116455,
            "question": "Is David LaChapelle a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9041078090667725,
            "question": "What other films has David LaChapelle directed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8796637654304504,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'Rize'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8510027527809143,
            "question": "Name a film by David LaChapelle."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7200635671615601,
            "question": "What is the name of the director who made 'Rize'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.565582275390625,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in David LaChapelle's films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37918588519096375,
            "question": "Is 'Rize' a documentary or a fictional film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3585256338119507,
            "question": "When was the film 'Rize' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3084973692893982,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'Rize' likely to be?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The director of the film 'Rize' is David LaChapelle.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3717_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the film 'Rize' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3717_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'Rize' a documentary or a fictional film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3717_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes explored in David LaChapelle's films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3717_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3717_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3717_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3717_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3717_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3717_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3717_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3717_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3717_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3717_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3717_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the required JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all four documents mention that David LaChapelle directed the dance/music documentary film RIZE, which is also known as 'Rize'."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that confirms David LaChapelle directed the film \"Rize,\" which supports the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}